{
    "id": "2c3310b485c74c8c8658ef2efe5b2e01",
    "title": "Past Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… college last year.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to say when something happened in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "was leaving",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb5708cd47504b7b956f281769a9903d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team ………………………… them yesterday.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to say when something happened in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "had defeated",
                "defeated",
                "was defeating"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85c04a2cdedf4e99b466d21f68cfe3ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. TV when dad arrived.",
            "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about an action or situation that was going on at a particular point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "was watching",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd8d8d26e90f471c92e6c25f8f30a975"
        },
        {
            "question": "After she …………………………. her breakfast, she went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ate",
                "had eaten",
                "was eating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a12a41053f644fd1b70c9f9de36efc6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the time I reached the station, the train …………………………..",
            "description": "The past perfect is used for the earlier of two past actions/ ",
            "answers": [
                "departed",
                "had departed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f2d3a68f5c24f05aeb29b122d9237d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… here yesterday.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to say when something happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "came",
                "had come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d96f9b4eaa744fb6af97da84ae0a5304"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… home late when the accident occurred.",
            "description": "The past continuous is used for the longer background action that was going on when another action took place.",
            "answers": [
                "drove",
                "was driving",
                "had driven"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d53061c5bbf406bbfdff128a11653b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The guests had left before I ………………………… home.",
            "description": "We use the simple past for the later of the two past actions.",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "was reaching",
                "had reached"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f8e877c12a5947a99bc0edcbc007b16b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. sleep well last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc2c9a1803e84e6386aa2887dc31a029"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every morning, he …………………………. for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was going",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1ac6f4a19e584d29bbd5c1db8d112257"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………… when she heard the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was weeping",
                "wept",
                "had wept"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b20b05bb08948a7a6ab15ca0fd96684"
        },
        {
            "question": "I thought of it just when you …………………………….. your mouth.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about two simultaneous short actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "was opening",
                "had opened",
                "opened"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aae4083dbec64ca0ac4416da38707222"
        }
    ]
}